aimgroup.com 2019-08-30

# Privacy Policy | AIM Group

### **Our Privacy Policy (Version 1.0, 11 May 2018)**

We are committed to protecting your privacy.  

#### **What you need to know about us**

We are the Advanced Interactive Media Group LLC, also known as the AIM Group. We also use the trade names Classified Intelligence and Classified Intelligence Report. Our services, and therefore this policy, are aimed at business professionals involved with digital marketplaces and related industries. We are registered in Florida. Our registered address is 402 Spring Valley Road, Altamonte Springs, Florida 32714, United States. You may contact us by post at this address, by email at [info@aimgroup.com](mailto:info@aimgroup.com) or by phone on +1.407.788.2780.  

#### **The information we collect and how we use it**

_Information provided by you or your company_ When you register on AIMGroup.com for news and information updates; event or service details; to book an event; buy a report or service; download content or complete a survey, you may be asked to tell us who you are and give us details, e.g. your name, email address, phone number, company, job role, billing address. You or your company may also have provided such information in relation to a purchase of our services by phone, email, post or in person, e.g. at a business meeting or event. We may use information you provide to contact you regarding your service, enquiry, booking or any matter relating to AIM Group services, your request or your use of this website. We may also use it to provide you with the services you or your company have requested from us, to manage your account and to contact you about other services we think may be of interest to you. _Use of cookies_ Our website uses Cookies. These are small data files sent from a server computer during an online browsing session. Cookies are typically stored on your computer’s internal storage and are used by Websites to simulate a continuous connection to that site. To make our site more responsive to your needs we use Cookies to track and manage information relative to your specific interests. In this way we can tailor our site to your needs, deliver a better and more personalized service, and track the pages you visit on our site. Cookies automatically identify your browser to our computers when you interact with our site. Your browser options may allow you to disable cookies. Please note: If you disable cookies, you may not be able to access all the services on our site.  

#### **Who we share your data with**

We store and process your information on computers and cloud services in the United States, European Union, and elsewhere in the world depending on our data service providers. The types of service providers we use for our business operations who process your data under our control include:

**Type of data processor** | **Processors at the date of this policy version**  
---|---  
Cloud providers that help us store and process your information | WPEngine, Inc. Intuit (Quickbooks)  
Website analytics providers that help us understand who is visiting our website | Google  
Payment service providers that process your payment information on our behalf | Stripe, Inc. PayPal, Inc.  
Partners who help us administer and market our own and our joint venture conferences | Rising Media VNG – Vertical Networks Group  
Cloud service providers who provide event registration, networking and billing services | Eventbrite Swoogo Whova  
Customer Relationship Management cloud system providers that help us manage your data for sales and marketing purposes | Salesforce.com    
Email software providers that help us format and send emails to you and analyse the performance of email campaigns | MailChimp (Rocket Science Group)  
Cloud service providers who host our office software and business email system | Google  
  
We may change the specific providers listed above from time to time without updating this policy. In processing orders, we may send your details to, and also use information from, credit reference agencies and fraud prevention services. We do not maintain credit card information on file.  

#### **Sharing your data with third parties**

Should you register for any AIM Group event or download any third-party content, we may pass your contact information to parties that either a) are partners in the event in question or b) are providers of the content you have downloaded. When you register for an event or access certain content, you will be reminded your data may be shared with named third parties. We may also share your details under special circumstances such as when we believe in good faith that it is required by law. **How long we keep your personal information** We keep your personal information in line with our data-retention policy. This means that we will remove data which we have collected directly from you from our systems if: (i) you are not subscribed to any of our email updates or other services; _and_ (ii) we haven’t had any direct contact with you for more than 36 months. (This period typifies the maximum length of time that a contract could be in discussion / negotiation with us). For personal data provided to us, if any, by your company and / or any of our clients, we may be governed by individual data retention agreements with your company / the client. In certain circumstances, we have a statutory obligation to keep your personal information for a set period of time, and we will retain it accordingly. We may retain financial information needed for auditing purposes for up to seven years or otherwise as required by law.  

#### **How to keep your personal information up-to-date**

We want your personal information to be accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove inaccurate information. Please email amendments to [ **privacy@AIMGroup.com**](mailto:privacy@AIMGroup.com). We will contact you to verify your identity and, once confirmed, make the changes.  

#### **How you can find out about the information we hold about you**

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email [privacy@aimgroup.com](mailto:privacy@aimgroup.com) or write to us at the address above. We will get in contact to verify your identity and, once verified, If we do hold information about you we will:

  * give you a description of it
  * tell you why we are holding it
  * tell you who it could be shared with
  * provide you with a concise and clear copy of the information

#### **Our legal basis for processing your personal information**

Much of our processing will be under the basis of “contractual obligation.” In other words, we need and use your personal information to provide services you or your company have requested from us or have contracted us to provide. However, when we communicate with you regarding products and services you may be interested in receiving from us or from current or potential partners, our basis for processing is our legitimate interest. As we are communicating with you in the context of your corporate activity and identity and not in relation to your private life, we believe this is reasonable and fair in the context of our audience. Of course, you always have the option to object, unsubscribe from our communications, and / or have your details removed as detailed below.  

#### **Asking us to suppress or remove your personal information**

If you do not want to receive information from us in the future you can quickly ask us to stop emailing you by clicking the unsubscribe link you will find on many of our service and marketing e-mails or by sending your details to [ **privacy@AIM Group.com**](mailto:privacy@dataiq.co.uk). If, additionally, you want us to remove your information entirely (and assuming we have no other obligation to keep it) please let us know and we will do this – but we would encourage you to let us continue using it for suppression purposes only, i.e. as a record that you do not want to receive further information from us.  

#### **What to do if you have a complaint**

If you have a complaint about our handling of your data, send it to [**privacy@AIMGroup.com**](mailto:privacy@AIMGroup.com) and we will deal with your request promptly. If you are not satisfied with the way your complaint was handled, you can refer your complaint to the relevant data protection regulator in your country or elsewhere in the world.  

#### **Links to other websites**

Our website may link to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website and the data AIM Group holds on you in its systems, so when you visit other websites, you should read their privacy policies.  

#### **Sale of business**

If this business is sold or integrated with another business your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers’ advisers and will be passed on to the new owners of the business. It is therefore intended that any consents given above or on the relevant pages will benefit any purchaser of our business.  

#### **Your use of our services**

Please be sure you are aware of these policy terms while you use our site. If our terms change, the new terms will be shown on this page, and we may place notices on other pages of the website to make you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it.
